Hello friends, ICICI Lombard General
's results are out and they will look very good on the year-on-year and
quarter-on-quarter front
because the
total income which was Rs 2850 crore last year
increased to Rs 3489 crore this year and in the last quarter
it was Rs 3058 crore. There has been an increase in the total income on both year-on-year and
quarter-on-quarter basis
and the
profit friends, which was Rs 281 crore last year,
increased to Rs 300.45 crore this year and Rs
313 crore in the last quarter. So friends, this is the
only place where
after listing, CD is being seen on the positive side and the
growth in the company is also seen to be very good
and those who have this
can definitely fold this experiment
and this time friends, we have
also announced a dividend of four times more, so you should also consider this.